http://www.summerjobs.com/privacy.html

AboutJobs.com, Inc. Privacy Statement
This privacy statement applies to:
www.summerjobs.com
Your use of and access to this site is subject to AboutJobs.com, Inc. Terms of Use Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online from users of this website. This policy details what kind of information we collect, when and how we use that information, and the choices you have with respect to how you choose to share your personal information.
AboutJobs.com, Inc. does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. AboutJobs.com, Inc. only collects personally identifiable information from resume postings, the registration process for posting jobs, and mailing list registrations.
AboutJobs.com, Inc. respects your right to privacy. As part of the registration process, we give you the opportunity to decline to receive any mailings from either AboutJobs.com, Inc. or other parties to whom the AboutJobs.com, Inc. may provide such information. Your personally identifiable information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection.
AboutJobs.com, Inc. reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. AboutJobs.com will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, users should be aware that AboutJobs.com may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through a link on an AboutJobs.com site.
AboutJobs.com, Inc. is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information.
Use of Cookies
Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of AboutJobs.com's web servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. AboutJobs.com, Inc. uses cookies for to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. Users should be aware that AboutJobs.com cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties using AboutJobs.com to display content.
If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature.
Upon request, AboutJobs.com will allow any user to "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time. Additionally, upon request, AboutJobs.com will use reasonable efforts to allow users to update/correct personal information previously submitted which the user states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Also, upon a user's request, AboutJobs.com will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from its database; however, it may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions.
AboutJobs.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
